[
  {
    "question": "What color is the sky?",
    "answers": ["blue"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many letters are there in the alphabet?",
    "answers": ["26", "twenty-six", "twenty six", "twentysix"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of carbon?",
    "answers": ["12.0096", "12.0116"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of lithium?",
    "answers": ["6.938", "6.997"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of berylium?",
    "answers": ["9.0121831"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of boron?",
    "answers": ["10.806", "10.821"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of hydrogen?",
    "answers": ["1.00784", "1.00811"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of nitrogen?",
    "answers": ["14.00643", "14.00728"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of oxygen?",
    "answers": ["15.99903", "15.99977"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of flourine?",
    "answers": ["18.998403163"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of neon?",
    "answers": ["20.1797"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of sodium?",
    "answers": ["22.98976928"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of magnesium?",
    "answers": ["24.304", "24.307"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of aluminum?",
    "answers": ["26.9815385"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of silicon?",
    "answers": ["28.084", "28.086"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of phosphorus?",
    "answers": ["30.973761998"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of sulphur?",
    "answers": ["32.059, 32.076"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of chlorine?",
    "answers": ["35.446", "35.457"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of argon?",
    "answers": ["39.948"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of potassium?",
    "answers": ["39.0983"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of calcium?",
    "answers": ["40.078"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of scandium?",
    "answers": ["44.955908"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of titanium?",
    "answers": ["47.867"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of vandium?",
    "answers": ["50.9415"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of manganese?",
    "answers": ["54.938044"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of iron?",
    "answers": ["55.845"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of cobalt?",
    "answers": ["58.933194"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of nickel?",
    "answers": ["58.6934"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of copper?",
    "answers": ["63.546"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of zinc?",
    "answers": ["65.38"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of gallium?",
    "answers": ["69.723"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of germanium?",
    "answers": ["72.630", "72.63"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of arsenic?",
    "answers": ["74.921595"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of selenium?",
    "answers": ["78.971"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of bromine?",
    "answers": ["79.901", "79.9071"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of krypton?",
    "answers": ["83.798"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of rubidium?",
    "answers": ["85.4678"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of strontium?",
    "answers": ["87.62"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of yttrium?",
    "answers": ["88.90594"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of zirconium?",
    "answers": ["91.224"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of nobium?",
    "answers": ["92.90637"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of molebdenum?",
    "answers": ["95.95"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of technetium?",
    "answers": ["97"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of ruthenium?",
    "answers": ["101.07"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of rhodium?",
    "answers": ["102.90550", "102.9055"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of palladium?",
    "answers": ["106.42"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of silver?",
    "answers": ["107.8682"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of cadmuium?",
    "answers": ["112.414"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of indium?",
    "answers": ["114.818"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of tin?",
    "answers": ["118.710", "118.71"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of antimony?",
    "answers": ["121.760", "121.76"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of tellurium?",
    "answers": ["127.60", "127.6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of iodine?",
    "answers": ["126.90447"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of xenon?",
    "answers": ["131.293"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of cesium?",
    "answers": ["132.90545196"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of barium?",
    "answers": ["137.327"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of lanthanum?",
    "answers": ["138.90547"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of cerium?",
    "answers": ["140.116"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of prasydymium?",
    "answers": ["140.90766"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of neodymium?",
    "answers": ["144.242"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of promethium?",
    "answers": ["145"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of smarium?",
    "answers": ["150.36"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of europium?",
    "answers": ["151.964"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of gadolinium?",
    "answers": ["157.25"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of terbium?",
    "answers": ["158.92535"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of dysprosium?",
    "answers": ["162.500", "162.5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of holmium?",
    "answers": ["164.93033"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of erbium?",
    "answers": ["167.259"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of thulium?",
    "answers": ["168.93422"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of ytterbium?",
    "answers": ["173.045"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of lutetium?",
    "answers": ["174.9668"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of hafnium?",
    "answers": ["178.49"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of tantalum?",
    "answers": ["180.94788"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of tungsten?",
    "answers": ["183.84"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of rhenium?",
    "answers": ["186.207"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of osmium?",
    "answers": ["190.23"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of iridium?",
    "answers": ["192.217"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of platinum?",
    "answers": ["195.084"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of gold?",
    "answers": ["196.966569"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of mercury?",
    "answers": ["200.592"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of thallium?",
    "answers": ["204.382", "204.385"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of lead?",
    "answers": ["207.2"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of bismuth?",
    "answers": ["208.98040", "208.9804"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of polonium?",
    "answers": ["209"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of astatine?",
    "answers": ["210"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of radon?",
    "answers": ["222"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of francium?",
    "answers": ["223"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of radium?",
    "answers": ["226"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of actinium?",
    "answers": ["227"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of thorium?",
    "answers": ["232.0377"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of protactinium?",
    "answers": ["231.03588"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of uranium?",
    "answers": ["238.02891"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of neptunium?",
    "answers": ["237"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of plutonium?",
    "answers": ["244"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of americum?",
    "answers": ["243"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of curium?",
    "answers": ["247"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of berkelium?",
    "answers": ["247"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of californium?",
    "answers": ["251"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of einsteinium?",
    "answers": ["252"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of fermium?",
    "answers": ["257"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of menelevium?",
    "answers": ["258"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of nobelium?",
    "answers": ["259"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of lawrencium?",
    "answers": ["262"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of rutherforium?",
    "answers": ["263"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of dubnium?",
    "answers": ["268"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of seaborgium?",
    "answers": ["271"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of bohrium?",
    "answers": ["270"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of hassium?",
    "answers": ["270"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of meiterium?",
    "answers": ["278"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of darmstadtium?",
    "answers": ["281"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of roentgenium?",
    "answers": ["281"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of cobernicium?",
    "answers": ["285"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of ununtrium?",
    "answers": ["286"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of flerovium?",
    "answers": ["289"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of ununpentium?",
    "answers": ["289"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of livermorium?",
    "answers": ["293"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of ununseptium?",
    "answers": ["294"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the atomic weight of ununoctium?",
    "answers": ["294"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Latin name for the common mouse?",
    "answers": ["Mus musculus"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Pilgrims never called themselves Pilgrims, what were they?",
    "answers": ["Separatists"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What juice is distilled to make cachaca?",
    "answers": ["Sugarcane"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What mid-western state shares its name with the title of a 1982 Bruce Springsteen album?",
    "answers": ["Nebraska"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the movie \"Mean Girls\", what does Lindsay Lohan's character dress up as for a Halloween Party?",
    "answers": ["Bride of Frankenstein"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which river made the Grand Canyon?",
    "answers": ["Colorado River"]
  },
  {
    "question": "On Christmas Day 800 A.D., who was coronated as emperor of the Holy Roman Empire?",
    "answers": ["Charlemagne"]
  },
  {
    "question": "At which pole would you find penguins?",
    "answers": ["The South Pole", "South", "South Pole"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What TV show featured the fictional band \"The Be Sharps\"?",
    "answers": ["The Simpsons", "Simpsons"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who coined the phrase \"slam dunk\"?",
    "answers": ["Chick Hearn", "Hearn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Entomologists study what?",
    "answers": ["Insects", "Insect"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What would you suffer from with Hypotension?",
    "answers": ["Low blood pressure", "blood pressure"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first Republican US President?",
    "answers": ["Hannibal Hamlin", "Hamlin", "Abraham Lincoln", "Lincoln"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What literary work inspired Jefferson Airplane's \"White Rabbit\" song?",
    "answers": ["Alice in Wonderland"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bristol, Rockingham, Chelsea, and Minton are types of what?",
    "answers": ["Pottery porcelain in China", "Chinese pottery", "Chinese porcelain"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What legendary rock band had a drummer nicknamed \"Bonzo\"?",
    "answers": ["Led Zeppelin"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. (Doc) Brown's puppy in \"Back to the Future Part II\" was named after what astronomer?",
    "answers": ["Copernicus", ""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ambergris is a waxy substance that originates as a secretion from what animal?",
    "answers": ["Sperm whale", "Whale"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who invented the rubber band?",
    "answers": ["In 1845, Stephen Perry, of the rubber manufacturing company Messers Perry and Co., invented the rubber band.", "Stephen Perry", "Perry", "Messners", "Messners & Perry", "Messners and Perry"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous actor is honored with a statue in Leicester Square?",
    "answers": ["Charlie Chaplin", "Charles Chaplin"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What strait separates Spain from Morocco?",
    "answers": ["Strait of Gibraltar", "Gibraltar", "Strait of Gibralter", "Gibralter"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was the candy apple invented?",
    "answers": ["New Jersey", "Jersey"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many life boats were on board the Titanic?",
    "answers": ["20", "Twenty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Triskaidekaphobia is the fear of what?",
    "answers": ["The number 13 -- The phobic avoids anything dealing with 13. He might refuse to step out of his homes on the 13th of every month.", "The number 13", "13", "Thirteen"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Seinfeld creator plays himself in the TV show \"Curb Your Enthusiasm\"?",
    "answers": ["Larry David", "David"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is it called when the liquid vapor pressure equals to the pressure of the gas above it?",
    "answers": ["Boiling point", "Boiling"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which U.S. city is known as \"The Emerald City\"?",
    "answers": ["Seattle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Fauna refer to?",
    "answers": ["Animal life", "Animals"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which band released the song \"Proud Mary\" in 1969?",
    "answers": ["Creedence Clearwater Revival", "Creedence Clearwater", "Creedence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What popular one-named musician's last name is Armstrong?",
    "answers": ["Dido"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which decade did the movie \"Casablanca\" premier?",
    "answers": ["1940s", "1940's", "40's", "40", "forties", "the forties", "1940"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was writer and war hero T.E. Lawrence popularly known as?",
    "answers": ["Lawrence of Arabia", "Lawrence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What model was married to musician Nikki Sixx?",
    "answers": ["Donna D'Errico", "D'Errico"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was nylon first synthesized?",
    "answers": ["1935"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Greek mythology, who did Athena turn into a spider?",
    "answers": ["Arachne"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which shark has seven gill slits, as opposed to the normal five?",
    "answers": ["The sevengill shark", "sevengill shark", "sevengill"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What slang term for the stomach is the highest-scoring ailment in the game \"Operation\"?",
    "answers": ["The breadbasket", "The bread basket", "The bread-basket", "Breadbasket", "Bread basket", "Bread-basket"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Orient Express train originally ran from Paris to where?",
    "answers": ["Istanbul"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the largest meteorite crater on Earth?",
    "answers": ["Vredefort, South Africa -- 299 km diameter", "Vredefort"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Rolling Stones hit was reputedly based on Martha Reeves and The Vandellas \"Dancing In The Street\"?",
    "answers": ["I can't get no satisfaction", "Can't get no satisfaction", "Satisfaction"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the principle holiday adornment in most Mexican homes?",
    "answers": ["el Nacimiento, the Nativity scene", "el Nacimiento", "the Nativity scene"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who said, \"Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity, and I'm not sure about the universe\"?",
    "answers": ["Albert Einstein", "Einstein"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Titanic picked up passengers in which two ports other than Southampton?",
    "answers": ["Cherbourg and Queenstown"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name for a virus that infects a bacteria?",
    "answers": ["Bacteriophage"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What American street is best known for its eight switchbacks between Hyde and Leavenworth?",
    "answers": ["Lombard Street", "Lombard"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rome was founded in which year?",
    "answers": ["753 B.C", "753 BC", "753BC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The song \"I'll Be Missing You\" is a tribute to who?",
    "answers": ["The Notorious B.I.G.", "Notorious B.I.G.", "The Notorious BIG", "Notorious BIG"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first woman to reach the summit of Mount Kilimanjaro?",
    "answers": ["Sheila MacDonald -- She ascended the Tanzanian mountain in 1927 at the age of 22.", "Sheila MacDonald", "MacDonald"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which U.S. state is known for its Juicy Lucy burgers?",
    "answers": ["Minnesota", "Mn"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Christmas song, The Holly and The Ivy which one bears the crown?",
    "answers": ["The holly", "Holly"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In The Simpsons, who said: \"I've said it before and I'll say it again: Democracy simply doesn't work.\"?",
    "answers": ["Kent Brockman", "Brockman"]
  }
]

